在教会里
In the church,
人们常常不知道如何与周围
we often don’t know how to relate to
正在挣扎的朋友或... 家人建立起联系
friends or... or family members who are struggling.
这意味着很多人 甚至我们教会中的人
That means a lot of people, even in our church,
都是孤独的
feel really alone.
因此让我们示以他们爱
So let's show them our love
让我们在上帝的关怀下为这些孩子送行
and send these boys off in the embrace of God's love.
乔·李 迈克尔·蓝道夫 本杰明·埃利斯
Joe Lee, Michael Randolph and Benjamin Ellis.
请上来
Come on.
嗯 就是你们
Yeah. That's right.
先生们 请跟我一起站到台上来
Gentlemen, please join me up here on stage.
布莱格堡 - 陆军空降兵与特种部队驻地
我们祈祷 亲爱的主
We pray, dear Lord,
请你保佑这些仗剑执盾之人...
for those that wield the swords so that...
并让正义得到胜利
that righteousness may triumph
让邪恶必然败亡
and wrongdoings may be vanquished.
对於这些保卫我们的人
For these men are our protectors.
请上帝你 能宽慰他们的家人
Lord, please comfort their families
当他们被派往前线驻派时
while these men are deployed.
请赐予所有这些孩子特别的恩典
Bestow special grace upon all these children.
愿上帝祝福你们 保佑你们
May God bless you and protect you.
愿上帝保佑美国 阿门
And may God bless America. Amen.
阿门
Amen.
对不起 我并不想吵醒你的
Sorry. I didn’t want to wake you up.
没关系 我早已经醒了
That's all right. I was already awake.
训练进行得怎样了
How's training going?
我们是否还有时间来滚个床单
Do we have time for night sex or no?
我想他已经醒了
I think he's awake.
那他今天总要去学校吧
Doesn’t he have school today?
不 今天是周六
No, it's Saturday.
现在周六都不上课的吗
Aren’t they in school on Saturdays?
1953年起就不上了
Not since 1953.
我很喜欢1953年 那年头很棒
I liked 1953 a lot. It's a great year.
要跟爸爸打个招呼吗
Want to say hi to Dad?
爸爸 你手里拿的是什么
Hey, Dad. What you got there?
看看这个
Oh, look at that.
那是你在飞机上
That's you in the airplane. Mm-hmm.
这些是云彩
And those are the clouds.
他一整周都在忙着画这个给你
He's been working on that all week for you.
画的真棒
That's incredible.
过来帮帮我 好的 来吧
Give us a hand. Okay. Come on.
杰克  你在哪呢  我就在你身后 爸爸
Jack? Jack? I’m right behind you, Dad.
杰克  你在哪呢  爸爸 我就在这
Jack? Jack? Dad, I’m right here.
加油 你能行的
Come on. You got this.
我相信你
I believe in you.
我就陪在这里 好吗
I’m gonna be right here, okay?
如果你需要什么 我就在你身旁
If you need anything, I’m gonna be right here.
好了 准备好没
All right. You ready?
没 嗯 你行的
No. Yeah, you are.
不 请不要离开我
No. Please don’t leave me.
我没有离开你 我就在这呢
I’m not leaving you. I’m right here.
杰克 看着我
Jack, look at me.
3... 2... 1
Three... two... one.
现在 放松 孩子 然后游向我这
Now, let go, son. Swim to me.
不 你能行的
No. You’ve got this.
就这样 放松 看着我
That's it. Let go. Eyes on me.
用脚打水
Use your feet.
就这样 你会游泳了 杰克
That's it! You’re swimming, Jack.
你会游泳了 加油
You’re swimming. Come on!
你做到了 杰克 你会游泳了 加油
You’re doing it, Jack. You’re swimming. Come on!
你游得很好 儿子
You did good, son.
妈妈 我做到了
Mom! I did it!
嗯 你做到了 我做到了
Yeah, you did. I did it!
爸爸 我想我会游泳了 你看
Dad, I think I can swim now. Look.
再来
Again!
快看看
Look at that.
7个月长高一英寸
An inch in seven months.
7个月长高一英寸 你觉得呢
An inch in seven months. How about that?
这很厉害吗  当然 很不得了了
Is that enough? That's a lot. That's perfect.
你好 我是负责账单管理的希拉
Hi, this is Sheila from Bills Recovery.
我就是想问下你们账单逾期的情况...
I just wanna check in with y’all on your past due paym...
信息已删除
Message deleted.
詹姆斯 听着 夥计 很抱歉打扰了你的周末
Hey, James. Listen, man, I’m sorry to ruin your weekend,
但指挥官在对全队进行检测
but the CO is testing the whole team.
我想你最好过来下
Uh, you better get down here.
陆军一级军士 詹姆斯·哈珀
Army Sergeant First Class James Harper.
请稍息 军士
At ease, Sergeant.
这位是我们的新指挥官 罗伯茨中校
This is our new CO, Lieutenant Colonel Roberts.
膝关节二度撕裂
Knee was shredded. Again.
康复进展得很好 谢谢 长官
Great job with the rehab. Thank you, sir.
你的肺部不再适合执行高空或水下任务
Your lung precludes high altitude or underwater operations.
这个肺陪我在5年中进行了4次战斗轮值 长官
I’ve done four combat rotations in five years with that lung, sir.
请放轻点 哈珀军士
You can relax, Sergeant Harper.
血检还显示 你体内药物残留有
Blood work came back filthy with Stanozolol,
康力龙 诺龙 苯丙酸诺龙 生长激素
Nandrolone, phenylpropionate and HGH.
你作为特种部队医务官
You’re an SOF medical sergeant.
你应该很清楚这些药
Should have known better.
我想留在队里 长官 我是为了想留在队里
I wanted to stay on the team, sir. I wanted to stay on the team.
我不知道为什么前指挥官会纵容你这样做
I have no idea what your previous COs encouraged,
但在我的治下我绝不允许
but I won’t accept that in my unit.
大队决定撤销你的特种部队军职
Big Army recommended a revocation of your Special Forces tab.
你这样的做法很不对 换我是不会这样做的
And although I disagree with your choices, I’m not going to do that.
你将会以荣誉退伍身份离开军队
You’re leaving the army with an honorable discharge,
但你将失去你的福利 其中包括你的退休金和医疗保险
but you’re losing your benefits, which include your pension and health care.
解散
Dismissed.
詹姆斯
James.
你用不着说什么 听着 他们无非想清理门户
- You don’t have to say anything. - Look. They’re cleaning house.
你不过是被抓了个正着 我认了 我能理解
- You made it easy for them. - I’ll own up. I understand.
以你的声誉
With your rep,
你退伍后肯定会有大把私人军事承包商来抢着找你
every private's gonna be hitting on you the second you walk off post.
我为膝盖吃了那些药 然后被血检发现了 这就是原因
I took shit for my knee. They found it in my blood. That's what it was.
就这样了  就再也没其他办法了
So that's it? And there's nothing you can do?
所以 他们就是临时搞个狗屁规则...
So, they just basically made up a new bullshit rule...
他们没有搞什么... 让测试...
- They didn’t make up a... - Test...
不 不是什么临时狗屁规则
No, they didn’t make up any bullshit.
你不说大队多年都没检测过任何人
You said they haven’t tested anybody in years.
是这样 就算他要搞 这也合情合理
They haven’t tested anyone in years. But it's legal.
这次检测纯粹就是新指挥官硬搞的...
It's the new CO that has a fucking hard-on for just...
我不知道 他无非想清理门户
I don’t know, he just wants to clear house.
这是上尉告诉我的 说他们想清理门户
That's what the captain told me. They wanna clear house.
这是什么
What's this?
催收公司寄来的
It’s, um, debt collectors.
但我已经和他们谈过了
But I already talked to them.
他们说 他们能为我们制定一个计划
And, uh, they said they could help us with a plan.
它们的利率是多少
What's the interest rate on it?
18%
It's 18%.
嗯 听着... 还有个工作可以干 而且能拿大把的钱
Yeah. There is... There's real work out there with real money.
私人承包商  嗯
Private contracting? Yeah.
不行 为何不呢
Mm-mmm. Why not?
不 你说过你不会去干这个的
No. You said you weren’t gonna do that...
我知道 我知道我说过什么
I know what I said. I know what I said.
不
No.
不行
Mm-mmm.
我爱你
I love you.
我是布鲁斯·迈克斯
This is Bruce Michaels
来自贴身保镖公司
with Executive Protection.
祝贺你从军队里荣誉退伍
Congrats on your years of decorated service.
我们很乐意为你提供工作
We’d love to discuss opportunities.
哈珀先生 我是大卫
Mr. Harper, my name is David.
我是从水电部打给你的
I’m calling from the Department of Water and Power.
信息已删除
Message deleted.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
我只是想在坏天气来之前...
Just putting up some shingles before...
把屋顶给修理好
before we get weather.
我们儿子呢
Where's our son?
他睡着了 今天给他累趴下了
Oh, he's asleep. He's down for the count.
他做的挺多 但...
Took him a bit, but...
学校... 在学校过得怎样
How was, uh... How was school?
你能先下来吗  嗯 就稍微等我一会
- Can you come down? - Yeah, I’ll come down in a second.
马上就快修完了
I just have a couple more to do.
亲爱的 我有事要告诉你
Honey, I got something to tell you.
我很快就弄完 不 现在就下来
- I’ll be down in a minute. - No. Like, now.
我说了很快就弄完 布瑞安
I’ll be down in a minute, Brianne.
梅森去世了
Mason's gone.
什么
What?
梅森 他去世了
Mason. He's gone.
我... 我才和苏珊谈完
I... I just talked to Suzanne.
怎么死的
How?
你觉得呢
How do you think?
葬礼在什么时候  明天
- When's the funeral? - It's tomorrow.
也许我们该打电话给你妈妈 让她来照看下杰克
Maybe we should call your mom and see if she can take Jack.
我不会去的
I’m not gonna go.
我们当然得去 布瑞安
Of course we’re gonna go, Brianne.
不 我不会去 因为我怕去了那联想到你
No, I’m not gonna go. ’Cause I can’t go to another one.
你到底在干嘛
What are you doing?
什么  你大半夜的跑屋顶上去到底是干什么
-What? -What are you doing on the roof in the middle of the night?
我在修理屋顶
I’m fixing the roof.
我很好
I’m okay.
我只是...
I’m just...
这正是梅森对苏珊所说的话
That's exactly what Mason said to Suzanne.
我现在真的很害怕
I’m really fucking scared.
我和我父亲不同
I’m not my father.
纹身
生日快乐
他会讨厌这个的
He would’ve hated this.
下葬仪式还是死亡
The ceremony or dying?
变得又胖又丑
Just being fat and ugly.
你觉得他们是如何把他那大屁股塞进棺材的
How do you figure they shoved his giant butt into that grave?
他穿的是丁字裤
He's wearing a thong.
他是怎么了
How’d he do it?
你是指什么
What do you mean?
他在睡梦中去世的
He died in his sleep.
家人有拿到全额赔付吗
The family get full payout?
拿到了
Full payout.
那就好
That's good.
乾脆去我那吃顿晚餐吧  不了
- Why don’t you come over for dinner? - No.
你还没看过我的新家呢
You haven’t seen the new house.
就这样说定了 你现在变得越来越无趣了
You’re coming to dinner. You’re as moody as he was fat.
去你的 也去你的
Fuck you. - Fuck you.
嗯
Yeah.
能见到你真好 很高兴你来了
Good to see you. Glad you’re here.
谢谢 你的家真漂亮
Appreciate it. You have a beautiful home.
夥计 玩的怎样了
Hey, bud. How's it going?
你要玩电子游戏吗
You wanna play a video game?
当然了... 我当然要来玩 看看这个
When do I... When do I not wanna play a video game? Look at this.
是白袜队
- Hey. - The White Sox.
嗯 漂亮
- Yeah. - Nice.
我喜欢白袜队 嗯 真没看出来
I love the White Sox. - Yeah. Apparently.
什么嘛  我是真喜欢白袜队 凯莉
- What? I like the White Sox. - Hey, Kelly.
詹姆斯叔叔
Hi, Uncle James.
明白了吗
You got that?
你是要带我参观 还是说要给我张地图
You gonna give me a tour, or should I just get a map?
我想是的
I guess so.
看好了
Watch this.
嗯 嗯 看我的
Yeah? Well, watch this.
投的真好 就犹如罗杰·克莱门斯 （*罗杰·克莱门斯：绰号"火箭人"  是活跃於1980年至2000年代的美职棒明星投手）
Really good arm. - Roger Clemens over here.
感谢你赐予我们这顿美餐
Thank you for this meal
以及感谢你把詹姆斯叔叔安全带了回来
and thank you for bringing Uncle James back safely.
阿门
Amen.
阿门 阿门
Amen. Amen.
谁才是最好的士兵 你还是我爸爸
Who was a better soldier, you or my dad?
嗯 你爸爸是我的长官 所以...
Well, uh, your dad was my chief, so...
小心你要说的话
Careful.
我是他的上级
I was his superior.
但我们呢....
Oh. But we were, uh...
该怎么说呢  我们彼此互相照应
How would you say? We looked after each other.
就像兄弟那样
Oh, kinda like brothers.
嗯 就像兄弟那样...
Yeah, kinda like brothers. Uh...
你真的有救了我爸爸的命吗
Is it true you actually saved my dad's life?
没有 是的
No. Yes.
有次 他把我从酒吧里拉出来
Once. He pulled me out of a bar once.
嗯 他喝醉了
Yeah, he was a wreck.
你父亲醉的爬都爬不起
Your father was an absolute wreck.
我可不想这么早就告诉你
I hate to break it to you this early.
我... 不 扫兴
I... No. - Bummer.
嗯 米奇喜欢棒球 但他永远都没法玩
Well, uh, Mikey loves baseball. He’ll never play.
他在抗争着呢 他...
He's fighting it. He’s...
看得出他很坚强
No quit in his DNA.
没法抗争赢的
There's no beating it.
嗯 就算最好的情况 他的余生都需要特殊照顾
Well, best case, he’ll need special care for the rest of his life.
你过得怎么样
How are you doing?
很好 嗯 很好
Good. Yeah, good.
嗯 你呢
Yeah. You?
嗯 我是说 也很好
Yeah, good. I mean, sure.
如果你真很好 你就不会失联两个月 所以怎么了
You don’t fall off the grid for two months if you’re good. What's up?
你对未来有什么期待
What do you look forward to?
看着我的孩子长大
Watching my kids grow up.
看着他们的笑脸
Seeing ’em smile.
为他们做最好的安排 给与他们我不曾拥有的
Making sure they’re set. Giving them the things I didn’t have.
我得把事情捋捋清楚
I gotta get my shit straight.
要帮忙嘛
There's help.
不 让我去干办公室的活  不 门都没有
No. Kill any operational future? No, not a chance.
私人承包商有联系我
Privates contacted me.
很好 嗯
Good. Yeah.
嗯 是的 这很好 你应该去赚这钱
Yeah. No, fuck yeah. You deserve a paycheck.
账单压我身上 我只能... 别想了 去干吧
Bank is on my ass, and I just... Hell yeah. Take it.
我曾经也去干过几次活
I pulled a couple of cowboy tours.
你懂的 干完之后 银行里的存款有了 买房子的钱也有了
You know, banked some decent cash, put a down payment on the house.
绿油油的钱 也就花个5 6天
Cash is real. You know, five, six a day.
还有奖金 这累积起来
Bonuses, you know, it adds up.
可是大把的钱
It's okay to cash in.
你知道吗  现在就纯他妈吃人的社会
You know, it's pure fuckin’ Darwin out here.
所以好好利用我们的所学去应对这环境
And we are trained to be ruthlessly adaptable. Use it.
反正在哪不都是给别人干
We’re all just mercenaries in the end.
所以你现在在哪里干 JSOC还是联邦机构 （*JSOC：美国联合特种作战司令部）
So what do you got going now? Is it JSOC? Agency?
在这之间
Uh, in between.
报酬虽没私人承包商给的高 但国家认可它的合法性
It doesn’t pay as good as private, but it's legit NatSec work.
他也出身於军队 人很好 非常可靠
He's one of us. Good people. Rock-solid.
有多少钱
How much?
35万
Oh, 350.
你能让我进去吗
Can you get me in?
你可是他妈和总统握过手的英雄
Fucking hero? President shook your hand.
去他的 他和很多人都握过手
Fuck off. He shakes a lot of hands.
结果他们就因为血检问题将我除名
They pulled my clearances because of blood work.
现在 只要你准备好 开口就行
At this level, as long as you’re good to go,
拉斯蒂并不关心你身体里打过什么
Rusty doesn’t care what you put in your body.
算我个
I’m in.
你想好了没有  我已经想好了
- Is that what you want? - That's what I want.
我破产了 迈克 我需要这活
I’m broke, Mike. I need this.
我会把你名字报过去
I’ll send your name up.
嗯
Yeah.
好的 我会安排会面
All right. I’ll set up a meet.
嗯 谢了
Yeah. Thanks.
没事
Of course.
没关系的
当只剩下我时
我还能说什么
他是哪里做错了
怎么样 夥计们  嘿 夥计
- What's up, fellas? - Hey, man.
这位是詹姆斯 我曾经的老队友 他在哪里
This is James, old running mate of mine. Where is he?
你知道他在哪里 你何不也顺带过来搭把手帮帮我们
You know where he's at. Why don’t you give us a hand every once in a while?
在18岁以前不停的辗转於男孩之家
长官 有没什么好吃的给我
Yo, Chief. Got anything tasty for me?
真他妈的甜
Like fucking candy.
切诺基紫番茄
Hmm, Cherokee Purple.
很荣幸见到你
It's an honor to meet you.
谢谢 长官
Thank you, sir.
别长官来长官去的 叫我拉斯蒂 拉斯蒂·詹宁斯
You can cut the "sir" crap. My name is Rusty, Rusty Jennings.
谢了 迈克
Thanks, Mike.
你介意帮我拿下靴子吗
Hey, you mind grabbing my boots?
戴夫
Hey, Dave.
你要来瓶啤酒吗
You want a beer?
不用了 谢谢
I’m good, thank you.
谢谢
Thank you.
迈克是我共事过最好的人
Mike's the best I ever worked with.
他说你是他共事过最好的人
He says you’re the best he's ever worked with.
是的 嗯 他... 他教会了我所知道的一切
Yeah. Well, he, uh... He taught me everything I know.
我们的声誉 是我们在这场游戏里唯一能留下的
Our reputation is the only commodity we got left in this game.
你看了我的故事
You reading my story?
你的 我的 迈克的 梅森的
Yours, mine, Mike’s, Mason’s.
我们都他妈有着同样的故事 甚至你父亲也是
It's all the same fucking story. Shit, even your father’s.
我父亲和这好像并没有关系
My father has nothing to do with this.
恕我直言
Due respect.
恕我直言... 他当然有
And due respect... sure he does.
我们把我们的思想 身体 精神交给了军队
We gave them our minds, our bodies and our spirit.
结果我们被他们用完即弃
And they chewed us up and spit us out.
留给我们的只有恐惧 愤怒 人生的不确定
Left us with fear, rage, uncertainty,
让我们感到失望 被抛弃 被背叛
disillusionment, a sense of abandonment, betrayal.
最后 我们变得自责 内疚
And finally, self-loathing and guilt.
把这些事的原因归咎到我们身上 搞得好像全我们的错一样
As if somehow, everything that happened to us was our own goddamn fault.
我完全理解你现在的处境 孩子
I know exactly where you are right now, son.
我曾和你一样
I was you.
妈的 我们都曾这样
Hell, we all were.
所以我们才要抱团取暖
That's why we started our own tribe.
我知道在你面前的路有很多
I know you got options in front of you.
如果你是想拿高薪的话
And if you’re looking for a big payday,
很多顶级公司都能给你
the top tiers can give it to you.
三叶丛林 宙斯盾 以及那头蠢猪 埃里克·普林斯
Triple Canopy, Aegis and that soulless fuck-pig, Erik Prince.
但我要你听听我的话
But I need you to hear me
因为都是真心的
’cause I mean this.
为这些公司做事 只会玷污你身上的荣誉
The stink from those gigs, it will rub off on you.
你到底想要说什么
So what is it that you do?
你是说你能为我提供不同的东西
You offer up something different or what?
你说对了
Damn straight.
我能给你真正的归属 光荣的工作
I can give you a real home, honorable work.
没利益往来 不为亿万富豪服务 也没任何狗屁事
No corporate interest, no babysitting billionaires, no bullshit.
我们根据法典第50条 受总统直接授权行事
We operate with direct presidential authority under Title 50.
严格处理涉及国家安全相关事务
Deal strictly with matters of national security.
我们隶属於秘密机构
A deep black OGA offshoot.
第50条 我熟悉的很
Title 50. I know those guys.
我们曾经也根据这条行事
We worked together downrange.
我们以进出口咖啡为掩护
We import and export coffee.
夥计 你当兵时干的那些活都是粗活
Man, what you did in uniform, sledgehammer shit.
我们干的是精细活
Our thing, scalpel work.
我们做事低调 雷厉风行 只有必要时才动手
High-speed, low drag, fangs only come out when they have to.
在柏林有一个威胁到我们国家安全的情况
There's a situation in Berlin that threatens our national security.
鉴於我们的存在属於机密
The team led by Mike will be fully black
迈克会领导一支秘密队伍前往
since our presence is not approved.
要多久
How long?
两周 顶多三周
Two weeks. Three, tops.
那么你怎么说 你愿意加入我们吗
So what do you say? You down for the cause?
嗯 当然
Yeah. For sure.
太好了 迈克和道尔顿会帮你搞定入职手续
Excellent. Mike and Dalton will walk you through the paperwork.
在此期间 布莱安和杰克显然...
In the meantime, Brianne and Jack obviously...
他们跟这个事有什么关系
Uh, what do they have to do with this?
嗯 等你回来之后
Well, when you get back,
希望我们大家能一起吃个饭什么的
be nice if we all got together and broke some bread.
现在 道尔顿会给你一张5万的支票
But for now, Dalton's gonna cut you a check for 50K.
这样你跟我们干起活来也能安心点
So you’re not sweating them while you’re working with us.
谢谢
Thank you.
你怎么白天关机了
Why was your phone off?
我找到份工作
I got a job.
你找到份工作
You got a job?
你找到份什么样的工作
What kind of job did you get?
就是那种工作
That kind of job.
为企业执行安保
It's babysitting corporates.
没什么危险的
It's not dangerous.
别再和我说了
Don’t tell me that.
我知道你在说谎
Now I know you’re lying.
不 我没有 看着我 我没有
No, I’m not. Look at me. I’m not.
宝贝 我得照顾好我的家人
Baby, I need to take care of my family.
你会错过杰克生日的
You’re gonna miss Jack's birthday.
飞机在8小时后起飞
Flight departs in eight hours.
亚历山大广场 停止战争
你花了超过15分钟才到这里
It take you longer than 15 minutes to get here?
我只花了8分钟
Only took me eight.
萨利姆·穆欣 42岁 病毒学荣誉教授
Salim Mohsin, 42. Professor Emeritus of virology.
在柏林洪堡大学
Humboldt-Universität, Berlin.
他每月都会上那里讲几次课
He lectures there a few times a month,
但他主要是从事研究工作
but his primary focus is research work
研究工作是在城东40公里处一个私人实验室进行的
which is conducted at a private laboratory 40 kilometers east of town.
威胁等级
Threat level?
生化恐怖主义 A级
It's bioterrorism. Category A.
车就在停车场 菲亚特Tipo
Car is in the parking lot. Fiat Tipo.
萨利姆
Salim?
终止监视 清理好现场 下午4点於#732会合
快起床了 早餐都弄好了
Wakey-wakey, eggs and bakey.
到锺起床了
Time to wake up.
都把任务简报记熟
Baseball cards stay here.
萨利姆·穆罕默德·穆欣 42岁
Salim Mohamed Mohsin. Age 42.
叙利亚裔 身高6尺1 体重190磅
Syrian descent. 6’1", 190 pounds.
胡子有染过 左耳位置后方有个心形胎记
Dyes his beard. Heart-shaped birthmark behind his left ear.
他的右手腕上也有圆形的胎记
Round-shaped birthmark on his right wrist.
哈佛医学院毕业 并获得联邦研究基金资助
Harvard Med. Graduates and receives a federal research grant
以研究人类史中的致病性流感病毒
to study pathogenic influenza viruses in humans.
H1N1以及其他亚种
H1N1 and avian flu mutations.
但资助未能被延长
His grant was not extended.
因此他和他家人搬到了柏林 在这里继续他的研究
His family relocated here to Berlin where he continued his research.
资助人是法鲁克·奥杰
Financed by Farouk Ojjeh,
奥达瓦的创始人 这是个与基地 叙利亚有联系的慈善机构
the founder of Al Dawaa, a charity with known links to al-Qaeda and Syria.
这是布局图
This is a layout
由我们内部线人提供
annotated by our inside asset.
该实验室只有很少的安保
The lab only has moderate security presence
因为警报装置是与柏林警方直连的
since the guard shack is connected to Berlin police.
实验室都什么样的门  不知道
-What kind of doors are they? -No idea.
那我们怎么进入  生物识别 保安的手指
How are we breaching? - Biometrics. Guard's thumb.
当目标人物被抓捕完后呢
What happens when we hit jackpot?
我们对他进行战术审讯
We conduct a tactical interrogation,
然后联系上级 等待进一步的指示
then contact higher and wait for further instruction.
大家从这片树林撤离后
Exfil back through the woods.
然后到这里会合
Link up with you here.
接着大家直接去机场
And then it's straight to the airport.
飞机会在1号停机坪准备好
Plane will be ready at Airfield Alpha.
我们都知道激进分子会干出些什么
We all know what one motivated radical can do,
所以让我们加油 完成任务 然后回到家人身边
so let's cowboy-up, get it done and go home to our families.
开始吧
Giddyap.
开始检查 野狼
- Go live. - Wolf Two.
狐狸
Fox Three.
马鲛鱼
Sierra One.
郊狼
Coyote One.
做好准备
Get ready.
还剩7分钟
Seven minutes.
起来
Up!
你们做什么
Was ist das?
站好
Stand up.
还剩6分钟
Six minutes.
我们要问你些问题
Need to ask you questions.
还有谁有实验室权限
Who has access to the lab?
只有我 只有我有权限...
Oh. Only me. I have access. It’s...
玛姬·博列夫斯基
Maggie Bolevska.
嗯 她是我的...
Y-Yeah. She's my...
她是我的研究助理 她也有权限
She's my research assistant. She has access.
还有谁知道你工作的具体内容
Who else knows the specifics of your work?
没人了 你们是什么人
Nobody. Who are you people?
你的资助人呢
Your financier?
嗯 他知道我的工作内容 但他...
Y-Yeah, he knows about my work, but he...
他不是科学家 他不过... 是个投资人 他....
He's not a scientist. He's a... He's an investor. He’s...
你把你的工作备份都放在哪
Where do you back up your work?
在离你家附近的地方 还有一对人马在待命中
There's another team on standby a block away from your family.
你最好合作 不然他们出什么事可不要怪我
Cooperate. There is no limit to what we are authorized to do.
你把你的工作备份都放在哪
Where do you back up your work?
全都在这 就在这些电脑里
It's all in here. It's in these computers.
没有其他备份了
There are no lines in or out.
我们拿到了
We got it. Payday.
如果你想要的是钱 我可以给你钱 这不是问题
If it's money you want, I can arrange money. It's really not a problem.
把他头转过去
Head against the wall.
我是说... 我真的可以...
I mean... I can really...
该死
Oh, shit.
耳机
Ears.
马鲛鱼刚触发了警报
Sierra just got a hit off the scanner.
警方正从柏林赶来
Police are inbound from Berlin.
等待牧场方面下达指示
Awaiting instructions from the ranch.
代号指令X
Code X.
不留活口
All the way?
All the way.
做成工业事故 我们还有五分钟
Industrial accident. We got five minutes.
把笔记本带上 去掉他们手铐和头套 我们从没到过这里
Bag the laptop. Lose the cuffs and hoods. We were never here.
搞定萨利姆
Get Salim.
大哥... 大哥 大哥 求你了 这整件事
Sir... Sir. Sir, please. This whole thing is...
就是个误会 我只不过... 是个搞科研的而已
It's a misunderstanding. I’m a... I’m a man of science.
这就是... 这就是个天大的误会
This is... This is a huge misunderstanding.
大哥 我真是搞科研的...
Sir! I’m a man of sci...
我是搞科研的 我还有家庭 求你了
I’m a man of science. I have a family, please.
大哥 求你了 我还有家庭 求你了
Sir, please. I have a family. Please.
不 不 不 不 停下 停下 停下 停下
No! No! No, no, stop, stop, stop, stop!
谁派你来的
Who sent you?
你甚至知道你在为谁工作吗
Do you even know who you’re working for?
你根本不知道你在做什么
You don’t know what you’re doing.
停下 求你了 听着
Stop! Please, listen.
我的研究将会拯救数百万人的生命
The research I’m doing will save millions of lives.
停下
Stop!
停下 停下 求你了
Stop. Stop, please.
如果你想要祈祷 现在可以开始了
If you wanna say a prayer, now is the time.
祈祷  我不相信什么神 我只相信科学
A prayer? I don’t believe in God. I believe in science.
听我说
Listen to me.
我的保险箱还有一份我所有数据的备份
I keep a copy of all my data in a safety deposit box.
如果你还有良知 就把它取出来
If you have a conscience, get it out.
世界将会需要它的
The world will need it.
停下 停下 求你 停下
Stop, stop. Please, stop.
请不要伤害我的家人
Please don’t hurt my family.
不要伤害我的家人 停下 求你了
Don’t hurt my family. Stop. Please.
不要 不要
Don’t! Don’t.
马鲛鱼 2分钟后接我们
Sierra One, RV in two.
收到
Copy.
我们要超时了 赶紧走
We’re in OT. Move out.
这里是马鲛鱼 一分钟后到
Sierra One. One minute.
草 是警察 9点钟方向
Fuck. - Cops,00.
站住 警察
Halt! Polizei!
移动
Move it!
移动中
Moving!
向你左侧
On your left.
狐狸中弹
Fox Two is hit.
压制住
Suppression.
包 把包丢我 收到
The bag. Throw it to me. - Copy.
把包丢我
Throw it to me.
草
Fuck.
狐狸倒下了
Fox Two down.
掩护我
Cover fire.
草
Fuck.
情况
Status?
左腿中弹
Left leg.
又有人来了
New contact!
马鲛鱼中弹
Sierra's hit.
放倒她
Put her down!
让我们离开这里
Let's get out of here.
起来 我们走
Come on. Let's go.
草
Fuck!
我的膝盖废了
My knee is fucked.
我要先把你放下来 妈的
I’m gonna have to set you down. Ah, fuck!
把装备丢了 能轻松些
Dump the gear, save the drive.
我扶着你 快走 快走
I got you. Come on, come on.
我们打死了警察
We shot cops.
我们是迫不得已
Did what we had to do.
笔记本没事吧
Is the laptop secure?
没事
It's secure.
我们拿到了笔记本 任务首位
We got the laptop. Mission first.
我必须给你输血 是A型血吗
I have to give you blood. Confirm A-pos?
是的
A-pos.
我们中得有人去送笔记本
One of us has to walk this in.
如果你不输血 你就会死的
If you don’t get blood, you’re gonna die.
你去送吧
You bring it in.
妈的 我不会丢下你
Fuck you. I’m not leaving you.
我的家人
My family.
我希望你能把我的事告诉克莉丝汀
I want Christine to hear about me from you.
你自己去告诉他们 迈克 你自己去和他们说
You tell ’em yourself, Mike. You’re gonna tell ’em yourself.
我要你答应我
I want it to be you.
我会带我们回家的 你听到没
I’m gonna get us home. You hear me?
现在我们将对柏林爆炸枪战案进行更深入的了解
With us now to shed more light on the explosion and gunfight in Berlin
有请安全专家威廉·索诺比
is security expert William Sonobe.
威廉 你能... 你能给我们一些关於案发现场的新信息吗
Uh, William, can you... can you give us any new information on this critical scene?
谢谢你邀请我 艾丽卡
Thanks for having me on, Erica.
美国政府正在积极向我们的
US officials have been active in offering aid
德国朋友提供援助和情报支持
and intelligence support to our German friends.
你不要再救我的命了
You have to stop saving my ass.
你现在欠我两回了
That makes two you owe me.
你他妈是怎么把我背出来的
How the fuck did you carry me out?
那么计划是什么
So what's the plan?
我们把笔记本带回去 拿到报酬 再去喝杯啤酒
We get the laptop home. Let's get paid. Let's have a beer.
收到
Roger that.
我不行了 你自己走吧
I’m down. You take it in.
不 不 说好的一起走
No, no. We go together.
我现在得改变下计划
I’ll compromise the mission.
我们不知道那个包里有什么
We don’t know what's in that bag.
把它带回去 你先走 我马上就来
Get it home. You go. I’ll catch up.
我去取得联系 然后再回来
I’ll make contact. I’ll come back.
嗯 回到这个四季酒店管道分店
Yeah. Back to the Four Seasons of Tunnels?
不用了 我没事的
Come on. I’ll be fine.
我会藏身暗处 我只是需要24小时来恢复下
I’ll move in the dark. I just need 24 hours to rest up.
赶快他妈走吧
Get the fuck outta here.
嗯
Yeah.
我去到柏林
- I head to Berlin.
把这个交出去
- Hand this off.
取得联系 安排好车 48小时后回家
Make contact. RV in 48. Forty-eight.
我会在瑟维纳酒店 安排好我们的东西
Hotel Salvina. I’m gonna get everything we need.
48小时
Forty-eight.
你不能被活捉
Capture's not an option.
不能被活捉
Not an option.
我游出去 直到我开始怀疑我还能否再游回来
I swim out until I start to wonder if I can make it back.
詹姆斯
James!
快点
Come on!
快点回来 孩子
Get back here, son.
你好 欢迎光临
Hallo. Willkommen.
取房
Uh, Ketner.
请出示护照
Reisepass, bitte.
非常感谢
Danke schoen.
是
Ja.
非常感谢
Mmm. Danke schoen.
已做好安排 这里很安全 上午10点见 药在床头柜里 6小时一次
Hallo?
谢谢
Danke.
你到底在哪里
Where the hell are you?
你好 嗨
Hallo. Hi.
我是拉斯蒂 说吧
This is Rusty. Go.
我用的一次性电话 并不安全
I’m on a burner. It's not secure.
收到
Copy that.
我们别无选择了 身体状况如何
We don’t have a choice. Physical condition?
受伤 但并不严重
Compromised but not critical.
野狼有与你联系吗
Did Wolf Two make contact?
野狼没能活着抵达柏林
Wolf Two never made it to Berlin.
我已经派了一支救援队前往酒店 然后带你去机场
I’ve got an extraction team en route to the hotel, get you over to the airfield.
你现在在哪
Confirm location.
你还在吗  你现在在哪
Hey, stay with me. Confirm location.
告诉我野狼的遭遇 我再告诉你位置
I’ll do that when you brief me on Wolf Two.
等你安全后 我会给你份完整报告
You’ll get a full brief when you’re secure.
现在情况已经变得不可收拾 我们已严重被暴露
Right now everything is extremely fubar, and we are highly exposed.
听我说 我现在所做的一切就是为了让你能回家
Listen to me. Everything I am doing right now is to get you home.
让你能安然无恙的回到牧场 你懂吗
Back to the ranch safe and sound. You feel me?
是 长官 当然 那就告诉我你在哪里
-Yes, sir. Of course. -Then confirm your location.
亚历山大广场 到处是警察
Alexanderplatz. Heavy police.
亚历山大广场 收到 这就来
Alexanderplatz. Copy that. Stand by.
现在让他们改道去艾尔森桥要多久
How long to reroute them to the Elsen Bridge?
15到20分钟
Fifteen, 20.
我需要你沿着水走
I need you to start heading for the water.
一直朝着埃尔森桥方向走 西北角 预计15到20分钟
Down towards the Elsen Bridge. Northwest corner. Fifteen, 20 minutes.
我是拉斯蒂 说吧
This is Rusty. Go.
我已经到达埃尔森桥 西北角
I’m at the Elsen Bridge. Northwest corner.
棕色宝马X1 看到没
Brown BMW X1. Confirm.
看到
Confirm.
收到
Copy that.
如果野狼没有到达柏林 那他是如何安排我撤离的
If Wolf Two didn’t make it to Berlin, how’d he arrange my exfil then?
听着 我知道 现在情形看起来很可疑
Look, I understand. Right now nothing makes sense.
但你要相信我 我现在正在帮你
But you gotta trust me. I am trying to help you.
你也这样帮的迈克
Same way you helped Mike?
你这混蛋 你是不是杀了他
You motherfucker. Did you kill him?
我们是在为谁工作
Who are we working for?
别再像个孩子一样 赶快他妈的上车
Stop acting like a child and get in the fucking car.
如果真是这样 我一定会杀了你
If this goes down, I’m gonna come for you.
快他妈的上车
Get in the fucking car.
草
Fuck!
你是美国人
You American?
你他妈海军陆战队的
You’re a fucking marine?
你海军陆战队的
Are you a marine?
曾经是 隶属侦察连
Was. Recon.
你的任务是什么
What was your mission?
营救
Extraction.
接着牧场发出了指令
Then the ranch gave an audible.
接到人后就处死
Terminate after pickup.
什么时候
When?
在桥上 我看到你的时候
On the bridge, when I saw you.
我搭档 是不是也是你干的
My partner, you go after him? Huh?
我听说他们把他带走了 抱歉
I heard they picked him up. I’m sorry.
他们说 我们是在拯救生命 但却是自相残杀
They told us we’d be saving lives, not killing our own.
我的... 照片 请还我
My... ...picture, please.
这里... 有一间安全屋
There is... There's a safe house.
用这个密码联络
Use this code for pickup.
拿着我的手机
Take my phone.
你绝不能回家去
You can never go home.
把确认指令Tomahawk
The kill code is Tomahawk.
发送过去 能为你拖延一阵
It’ll stop the team, at least for a while.
拉斯蒂说他会带我们发家致富
Rusty said he’d make us all rich.
他身上有没备份
快递
Kurier.
你好
Yes?
你是谁  你想要做什么
- Shh. - Who are you? What do you want?
你是谁
Who are you?
我来这并不想伤害你或你家人
I’m not here to hurt you or your family.
但如果你不回答我的所有问题 我会的
But if you don’t answer all of my questions, I will.
你丈夫把工作研究放在个保险箱里 我要知道它在哪
Your husband secured his work someplace safe. I need to know where.
希尔薇 看着我 看着我
Sylvie, look at me. Look at me.
想想雅尼斯和奥利维亚 快告诉我
For Yanis, for Olivier. Tell me where.
瑞士信贷银行 瑞士信贷银行
- Swiss Credit Bank. - Swiss Credit Bank?
就在保险箱里 保险箱里
- Safe deposit box. - Safe deposit box.
别伤害我儿子
Don’t hurt my son.
深呼吸 不会有事的
Shh, just breathe. It's gonna be fine.
让他去穿戴好 好的
- Tell him to get ready. - Yes.
你告诉他 我是他爸爸的老朋友 我们要一起去吃午饭
You tell him I’m an old friend of his dad’s, and we’re going out for lunch.
雅尼斯
Yanis.
我们走
Let's go.
他和我一起去
He's coming with me.
我们会在这里等你回来
We’ll be here when you get back.
你是他的朋友
You were his friend?
是的
Yes.
你难过吗
Are you sad?
是的
Yes.
我也是
Me too.
你们在哪认识的
Where did you meet?
巴黎
Paris.
你的头胎是在哪出生的
Where was your first child born?
我出生在... 闭上嘴
I was born... Tais-toi!
我还有两个孩子要养
I have two boys to raise.
我们所有一切都被你夺走了
Everything we have is in your hands.
回答我的问题
Answer the question.
雅尼斯出生在波士顿
Um... Yanis was born in Boston.
你打算为你第三胎取什么名字
What were you gonna call your third child?
乔丹
Jordan.
把车停下
Stop the car.
所以 他们付了你多少钱 嗯
So, how much did they pay you, huh?
我希望这值得你卖命
I hope it was worth it.
哪位
Yes?
侦察连 6-22-34 求救
Recon. 6-22-34. Mayday.
收到 位置
Copy. Location?
柏林
Berlin.
情况怎样
Condition?
可以移动
Mobile.
明天凌晨3点 GPS坐标 14.98 51.150
0300 tomorrow. GPS 14.98, 51.150.
你迷路了
Are you lost?
你介意把枪放下吗
Do you mind lowering the gun?
是你打给我的
You called me.
要上车就放下枪
It's the price of admission.
在崩溃之前
我们还能承受多少
你能不能别再挣扎了
There's no need to fight anymore.
我的包在哪
Where's my bag?
那么... 我们没事了
So... are we good?
没事了 你在这很安全
It's okay. You’re safe here.
我处理了你的膝盖 它感染得很严重
I cleaned your knee. It was badly infected.
你的ACL撕裂了 我不知道你怎么弄得 但你弄撕裂了 （*ACL：前交叉韧带）
You tore your ACL. I don’t know how you walked on it, but you did.
那个陆战队员告诉了我你的事...
The marine who told me about you...
你认识他
You know him?
不
No.
你杀了他吗
Did you kill him?
不 但我知道他们训练我们为他们跑腿
No, but I know they train us to run their errands.
杀死他们的敌人 甚至自相残杀
Kill their enemies and kill each other.
所谓"国家安全" 只不过是遮掩这一切肮脏勾当的借口
"National security." It's just a rock they can hide their dirty shit under.
我需要回去
I need to get back.
回哪去
Back where?
回家去
Back home.
别想了
That's done.
你再也回不去了
Home is a memory.
你需要... 你差点死了
You need... You almost died.
你的身体需要休息 我没事
- Your body needs rest. - I’m fine.
行了 我没事
- Shh. All right. - I’m fine.
雅尼斯 万一我无法亲口告诉你这些
Yanis, in case I’m not here to tell you this in person,
我爱你
I love you.
我知道在过去几年里 我一直缺席於你的人生
I know you have felt my absence these last few years.
我想要你知道原因
I need you to know why.
我很早就下定了决心
I made up my mind very early
我的孩子们绝不能生活在恐惧下
that my children would live without fear.
正因为如此 我选择了将我的一生献给科学界
And because of that, I chose to dedicate my life to science.
不幸的是 有些有权势的人不仅无视科学
Unfortunately, there are powerful people who ignore science,
甚至还为了自己的私利想利用它
even subvert it for their own personal gain.
雅尼斯 在你手中的是我毕生研究
Yanis, in your hands is my life's work:
可以预防致死率为16%的H5N1疫苗资料
the vaccine for the H5N1 virus with a mortality rate of 16%.
我因为它才坐在这里 对着这个摄像头却不是你的双眼
It may have landed me in this chair, staring into this camera instead of your eyes,
但我想让你知道 你的父亲在为一些东西奋斗
but I want you to know that your father stood for something,
我所奋斗的东西 只要能有你的帮助
created something that with your help
即便我被他们杀死后 仍将能造福於人类
will benefit humanity long after they’ve shot me down.
非常重要的是 如果恰巧爆发了疾病
It is very important that this vaccine is available
大众便能够免费使用到这些疫苗
free to the public should the unthinkable happen.
亲爱的主 感谢你赐予我这顿美餐
Dear Lord, thank you for this meal
并将我的客人安全带到这里
and bringing my guest here safely.
请宽恕我们的罪 让我们免於地狱业火
Forgive us our sins and keep us from the fires of hell.
愿我们灵魂能升入天堂
May our souls go to heaven.
特别是那些需要被怜悯的 阿门
Especially those in need of thy mercy. Amen.
阿门
Amen.
你的纹身 OD3224
Your tat. OD3224.
代表你服役於"矛头部队" （*矛头部队：用以泛指现在在战区前线参与打击任务的部队）
That's tip of the spear.
是的 他们让我们很忙
Yeah, they kept us busy.
在伊拉克还是阿富汗
In Iraq or Afghanistan?
两边
Both.
你去过兴都库什吗
You ever been to Hindu Kush?
山峰如此之高 你会认为彷佛天堂就在这之上
Mountains so high, you think heaven's resting on ’em.
山谷如此之绿 你会认为彷佛这就是伊甸
The valleys so green, you think it's Eden.
我才去时 还以为是来了科罗拉多州
I thought I was in Colorado when I first saw it.
你知道 我们曾连续12天为
You know, we were on a 12-day straight
寻找我们当地人的一个孩子
looking for one of our local guys’ kid.
打猎的时候 走失了... 没能找到他 可怜的家伙
Been gone... Gone hunting, couldn’t find him. Poor thing.
最后我们找到了个偏僻的院落 接着我们打开院门
So we broke down a door on this out-of-the-way compound,
然后冲了进去
and then we burst in.
在清查完房间后 我们找到了那个孩子
And once we cleared everything, we found him, the kid.
那个孩子 他被铁链锁在墙上 哭得很伤心
And he was chained to the wall, just crying his eyes out.
但在隔壁房 里面全是女孩
But in the next room, it's full of girls
四散躺着 全死了
all strung out, splayed out.
然后站在她们之中的是一只狗
And in the middle of all this was a dog.
一只小家伙
It's just a little thing.
曼吉 它很高兴
Mangy. Happy as can be.
它看到我们很高兴 它浑身脏乱 叫唤着
Happy to see us. All yelps and matted hair.
在这事件里 我唯一能记得的也就是那条狗了
And all that shit, and the thing I remember the most is the dog.
因为那条狗在经历这一切后仍然能做回它自己
’Cause that dog survived all that shit without even blinking an eye.
一死了之很容易
It's much easier to kill,
但要活着却很艰难
but it's harder to survive.
你在这里待多久了
How long you been out here?
13年了
Thirteen years.
你有家庭吗
You have a family?
嗯 我有个妻子 两个漂亮的女儿
Yeah, I’ve got a wife, two beautiful girls,
漂亮的房子
a nice house.
你不和她们联系吗
You ever feel like reaching out?
当我和她们一起...
When I reach out...
我总做错事
I break things.
我们都有心魔这东西
We all know the monster.
而它有时候会控制着你
And sometimes he comes to stay.
牛排怎么样
How's the steak?
我吃过更好的
I’ve had better.
我... 我也是
So... So have I.
美国人  是的
- American? - Yes.
一路安全 先生
Safe travels, sir.
我希望你能把我的事告诉克莉丝汀
I want Christine to hear about me from you.
你自己去告诉他们 迈克 你自己去和他们说
You tell ’em yourself, Mike. Tell ’em yourself.
你个混蛋
Motherfucker.
你来我家干什么
Doing at my house?
回答我
Answer me.
你要对我开枪吗
You wanna shoot me?
动手吧
Go ahead.
我上你家去告诉克莉丝汀 就像你让我做的那样
I went to your house to tell Christine, like you asked me to.
拉斯蒂说过... 你知道他想要除掉我的事吗
-Rusty said... -Did you know he was coming after me?
他说你没能幸存下来
He said you didn’t make it.
你为什么要骗我
Why did you lie to me?
骗你什么  去你的
About what? - Fuck you.
真正的归属 抱团取暖 光荣的工作
A real home. A tribe. Honorable work.
这本是为了抢劫数据 所有一切都不该发生的
It was a data heist. None of this was supposed to happen.
但它发生了 所以为了什么
But it did happen. And for what?
为了一票捞够
Payday of a lifetime.
我们偷的并不是数据
What we stole was not data.
是这些混蛋想要释放的病毒的解药
It's a cure to a virus these fuckers wanna release.
以便他们能在人们的痛苦中狂捞几十亿 你知道这个吗
So they can make billions off people suffering. Did you know that?
你他妈这样做良心过意的去
How do you fucking live with yourself?
我还要养家 尤其是我的儿子
I got a family and a son with special needs.
那我家人 我儿子 他们就不是了
So what about my family? My son! Their needs!
所有一切都安排妥当
Everything's taken care of.
将会有一大笔钱付给布莱安和你儿子 四百万
There's a huge payout to Brianne and your boy. Four million.
他们以后都将会衣食无忧
They’ll never want for anything ever again.
那我呢  我呢
Except for me! Me!
你不能回家去
You can’t go home!
他如果发现你在这里 他会用尽所有手段来对付你
He finds out you’re here, he's gonna come after you with everything he's got.
我们做了那么多
After everything we’ve done,
经历了那么多
everything we’ve been through.
我他妈的为你流血
I fucking bled for you!
结果我换来什么
And this is what I get?
詹姆斯 别这样做
James, don’t do this.
对不起
I’m sorry.
我父亲...
My father, uh...
他给我打上了同样的印记
He branded me to be like him.
你知道吗  我们他妈... 骨子里一模一样
You know, a fucking... a fucking Ranger to the bone.
当军队不再需要他 把他赶走的时候
And when they cut him loose and they cast him out,
他再也没回过家里
he just never came home.
从此消失 没有留言 屍体 他妈什么也没有
Vanished. No note, corpse. Fucking nothing.
我最后只能... 把那混蛋给我的全部东西都埋在后院洞里
I finally just buried all the... shit the fucker ever gave me in the backyard.
独自给他举行了葬礼
Had my own funeral.
我就站在那洞口前 可悲的看着他那些垃圾东西
I’m standing over this pathetic little hole filled with stupid shit.
然后对自己发誓 我永远都不要成他那样
And I swore to myself I would never be like him.
我永远都不会抛弃我的家人 你能懂这些吗
I would never forsake my family. Do you understand me?
如果拉斯蒂发现你在这
Rusty finds out you’re here,
他就会去对付你的家人
he's gonna come after your family.
要结束这事只有一个办法
There's only one way this ends.
怎么样  迈克
Hey, what's up, Mike?
你有啤酒吗  他在哪里
You got a beer? Where is he?
他在厨房里
He's in the kitchen.
我一直都想着能战死在沙场上
Always wanted to die with my boots on.
你做了正确的事
I got a room prepped and ready for ya.
我们要回家了 迈克
We’re going home, Mike.
放点该死的音乐
Put some fucking music on.
嗯
Yeah.
好冷
Cold.
告诉我...
Tell my s...
我儿子...
My son...
我没有碌碌而死
I didn’t die in my sleep.
我会的
I promise.
没事了
I got you.
冲啊 深水炸弹
Yeah! Cannonball!
嗯
Yeah!
游得不错
Good job!
杰克
Jack!